<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KartWheel</string>
    <string name="email">support@handstandwith.us</string>
    <string name="already_claimed_title">Invalid ticket</string>
    <string name="contact_us_subject_line">KartWheel - Android</string>
    <string name="contact_us_body">KartWheel - Android</string>
    <string name="scroll_down">Scroll down</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Let\'s go</string>
    <string name="tos">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="enter_code">Enter your ticket code</string>
    <string name="does_not_have_code">Don\'t have code? You\'ll either need to\n phone a friend
    or <a href="www.handstand.us/karwheel">get one online</a>!</string>
    <string name="already_claimed_explanation">Someone has already claimed this ticket! In order to use this code,
    they\'ll need to open up their app and forfeit their ticket.\n\nSo you\'re sure this is your ticket?</string>
    <string name="already_claimed_touch_here">Log in by touching here!</string>
    <string name="try_different_code">Try different code</string>
    <string name="tos_content">THE KARTWHEEL (\"EVENT\") WAIVER &amp; RELEASE OF CLAIMS, INDEMNITY
        AGREEMENT, ASSUMPTION OF RISK, AND CONSENT TO MEDICAL TREATMENT (\"WAIVER &amp; RELEASE\")\n\n
        PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CAREFULLY, AS IT AFFECTS YOUR FUTURE LEGAL RIGHTS. BY PROCEEDING
        WITH REGISTERING FOR THE EVENT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU HAVE CAREFULLY READ,
        FULLY UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS SET FORTH BELOW.\n\nThe following must be
        carefully read and signed in consideration of being permitted to enter (for any purpose) the
        Event and associated property (\"Premises\"). As used in this Waiver, the term \"Releasees\"
        is defined to include the following: (i) The California Corporation Team Handstand, its
        subsidiaries, affiliated companies, owners, members, managers, directors, officers, past and
        present employees, agents, representatives, successors and assigns (collectively, \"TEAM HANDSTAND\");
        (ii) the Premises owner(s); (iii) any Event volunteers; and (iv) any Event sponsors, sponsor\'s
        affiliates and contractors, and their respective employees.\n\nNOTE TO MINORS: If you are under
        the age of 18, you may only participate in the Event if accompanied by an adult, and only if
        a parent or guardian has reviewed, understood and agreed to the terms below.\n\nNOTE TO
        PARENTS/GUARDIANS OF MINORS: You acknowledge that you have reviewed, understood and agreed
        to the terms below (such terms being interpreted as if they applied both to you and your
        minor child/ward) and have the legal authority to enter into this Agreement on behalf of
        your minor child/ward.\n\nIN CONSIDERATION OF PARTICIPATING IN THE EVENT, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
        AND ANY PERSONAL REPRESENTATIVES, ASSIGNS, HEIRS, EXECUTORS, SUCCESSORS, NEXT OF KIN AND THOSE
        INDIVIDUALS WHOM I AM AUTHORIZED TO REGISTER FOR THE EVENT, I UNDERSTAND, AGREE AND REPRESENT
        AS FOLLOWS:\n\n1. I understand that the Event is an activity that may present danger, including
        but not limited to the risks associated with walking, running, biking, or taking public
        transportation.\n\n2. I expressly acknowledge and agree that the activities of the Event involve
        the risk of serious injury and/or death and/or property damage.\n\n3. I am fully aware of the
        risks and hazards inherent in participating in the Event and I voluntarily, knowingly and
        freely assume all risks associated with participating in the Event and entering the Premises,
        including, but not limited to, my own actions or inactions (or the actions/inactions of my
        minor child/ward), the actions or inactions of others (including Event attendees, staff or
        volunteers), falls, injuries, illnesses, infections, contact with others (including Event
        attendees, staff or volunteers), navigating any and all obstacles, Premises defects and the
        effects of weather, including, but not limited to, heat and/or humidity.\n\n4. I represent
        and warrant to Releasees that I am in good physical condition, am able to safely participate
        in the Event, and have no medical condition that would make my participation in the Event
        more hazardous to me or any other person.\n\n5. If I am pregnant, disabled in any way, or
        have recently suffered an illness or injury, I should have or did consult a physician before
        participating in the Event.\n\n6. I understand that it is my responsibility to obtain any
        insurance needed to cover personal injury or death and any liability I might incur to myself
        or cause to other Event participants.\n\n7. I consent to medical care and transportation in
        order to obtain treatment in the event of injury to me as TEAM HANDSTAND staff, volunteers or
        medical professionals may deem appropriate and understand that this Waiver &amp; Release extends
        to any liability arising out of or in any way connected with the medical treatment and
        transportation provided in the event of an emergency and/or injury.\n\n8. I agree to observe
        and obey all posted rules and warnings, to follow any instructions or directions, whether
        verbal or written, given by TEAM HANDSTAND through its employees, representatives or agents,
        and to abide by any decision of any Event official relative to my ability to safely participate
        in or attend the Event.\n\n9. I understand and agree that I am expected to exhibit appropriate
        behavior at all times while at the Event and to obey all local, state and federal civil and
        criminal laws while participating in or attending the Event. This includes, generally, respect
        for other people, equipment, facilities or property. TEAM HANDSTAND may dismiss me, without
        refund, should my behavior endanger the safety of, or negatively affect, the Event, Premises
        or any person, facility or property. I also agree to indemnify the Releasees from any and all
        third party claims caused in whole or in part by my negligent or intentional acts or omissions.\n\n
        10. I agree not to consume alcohol for six (6) hours prior to the Event or use any medicine 
        or substance that will inhibit my mental or physical ability to safely participate in the Event. 
        If I am of legal age and choose to drink during the event, I do so at my own risk. If I choose
        to consume alcoholic beverages after the Event, I will do so responsibly and only if I am over 
        the age of twenty-­one (21).\n\n11. I understand and agree that the Releasees are not responsible 
        for any personal item or property that is lost, damaged or stolen at the Event or on the 
        Premises.\n\n12. I consent to the use of my image in photographs, motion pictures or recordings 
        taken at the Event for use by TEAM HANDSTAND in its promotional activities for the event or 
        otherwise.\n\n13. I assign to TEAM HANDSTAND all rights, title, and interest in any and all 
        photographs, motion pictures, recordings or other records of the Event I may take or capture. 
        TEAM HANDSTAND grants to me a limited, non­exclusive right and license to use, for non­commercial 
        purposes only, any and all photographs, motion pictures, recordings or other records of the 
        Event I may take or capture at the Event.\n\n14. I understand and agree that any sale of 
        merchandise unauthorized by TEAM HANDSTAND is not permitted and I may be dismissed from the 
        Event and the Premises for selling such merchandise.\n\n15. I understand and agree that I may 
        not bring weapons, fireworks, or illegal substances to the Event or the Premises.\n\n16. I 
        understand and agree that all entry fees and ticket purchases are final and non­refundable.\n\n17. 
        I understand and agree that TEAM HANDSTAND reserves the right to change the Event venue, 
        location or date. In the event of such a change, there will be no refund of my ticket 
        purchase.\n\n18. I understand and agree that TEAM HANDSTAND reserves the right to cancel the 
        Event in the event of severe weather (including, but not limited to, heat, tornadoes, 
        earthquakes, fires, storms, lightning and floods), accidents, acts of war or terrorism, 
        military conflicts or riots, or for any reason that TEAM HANDSTAND believes will affect the 
        safety and security of Event participants and spectators. In the event of such cancellation, 
        there will be no refund of my ticket purchase.\n\n19. I recognize and acknowledge that there 
        are hazards and risks of physical injury or illness to Event attendees and that not all such 
        hazards or risks can be fully eliminated. I freely and voluntarily agree to assume the full 
        risk of death, bodily injury or property damage, regardless of severity, that I (or my minor 
        child/ward) may sustain as a result of my attendance at the Event, whether or not caused by 
        the active or passive negligence of the Releasees.\n\n20. I indemnify and hold harmless the 
        Releasees from any loss, liability, damage or cost they may incur while I am at the Event or 
        on the Premises, including attorney’s fees, if such loss or cost is caused by my active or 
        passive negligence.\n\n21. I release, waive, discharge and covenant not to sue the Releasees 
        from all liability to me, my personal representatives, assigns, heirs and next of kin, for 
        any claims, causes of action, obligations, lawsuits, charges, complaints, controversies, damages, 
        costs or expenses of whatsoever kind, nature, or description, whether direct or indirect, in 
        law or in equity, in contract or in tort, or otherwise, whether known or unknown, arising out 
        of or connected with my (or my minor child’s/ward’s) participation in or attendance at the 
        Event or while on the Premises, whether or not caused by the active or passive negligence of 
        the Releasees.\n\n22. I understand and acknowledge that the laws of the State of California 
        shall apply to all matters relating to this Waiver regardless of the Event location, that 
        the exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute with the Releasees resides in state or federal 
        court in San Francisco, California, and I expressly consent to the exercise of personal 
        jurisdiction in the State of California in connection with any dispute with the Releasees 
        arising from my Event participation or attendance.\n\n23. I expressly agree that this Waiver 
        and release is intended to be as broad and inclusive as permitted by the law of the State of 
        California, and that if any portion is held invalid, it is agreed that the balance shall continue 
        in full legal force and effect.\n\n24. I understand and agree that TEAM HANDSTAND may award 
        prizes of The Event to any and all teams it deems fit, and is not subject to any external or 
        internally facing rankings and scoring.\n\nHANDSTANDWITH.US/KARTWHEEL AGREEMENT AND LIABILITY 
        WAIVER (\"AGREEMENT\")\n\n1. I represent and warrant to TEAM HANDSTAND that I have full legal 
        authority to complete this Event registration on behalf of myself and/or any other person on 
        whose behalf I am registering (\"Registrant(s)\"), including authority to make use of the credit 
        or debit card to which the ticket purchase(s) will be charged. If I am registering a minor 
        under the age of eighteen (18), I represent and warrant that I am the parent or legal guardian 
        of that person and have the legal authority to enter into this Agreement on their behalf. By 
        proceeding with this registration, I agree that the terms of this Agreement shall apply equally 
        to them as it does for all Registrants.\n\n2.TEAM HANDSTAND shall not be liable for any direct, 
        indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages, including lost profits, resulting from 
        (a) the use or the inability to use https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel website, (b) any 
        transactions made or services or goods purchased through https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel 
        website, or (c) unauthorized access to or alteration of any transmissions or data.\n\n3. 
        Use of https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel website is at my own risk, on an \"as is\" and 
        \"as available\" basis, and TEAM HANDSTAND makes no warranty that its site or services will 
        be uninterrupted, secure or error free. I understand and agree that any material and/or data 
        downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel website 
        is at my own discretion and risk and that I will be solely responsible for any damage to my 
        own computer system or loss of data that results from the download of such material and/or 
        data.\n\n4. I agree to indemnify and hold TEAM HANDSTAND harmless from and against any and 
        all damages, costs, claims or demands, including reasonable attorneys\' fees, made by any third
        party due to or arising from or relating to my use of https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel or 
        the violation of any term of this Agreement.\n\n5. I understand that https://handstandwith.us/kartwheel 
        website is controlled by TEAM HANDSTAND from its offices in the State of California, United 
        States of America. By completing this event registration, I agree that the statutes and laws 
        of the State of California, without regard to conflict of laws principles, will apply to all 
        matters relating to this registration and Agreement. I further agree and expressly consent 
        to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of the State of California in 
        connection with any dispute or claim with TEAM HANDSTAND related to matters covered by 
        this Agreement.
</string>


</resources>
